André Ueckert

ueckert.andre@web.de +52 (222) 3684805 www.bestgermantranslator.com

Professional Freelance Translator for English-German and Spanish-German

Puebla, Puebla, Mexico

ALLROUND FREELANCE TRANSLATOR

Trilingual highly-creative and professional freelance translator, fluent in both oral and written English, German, and Spanish. Experienced in large-scale translations for global players such as Google, UpWork, Education First, and Jet Airways. Actively Accomplished translation management for IT firms and wholesale manufacturers in China.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Linguist

Google / UpWork, Mountain View

Jan 2015 - Current

Hired by UpWork to work as a German linguist on Google's translation, data annotation, and speech recognition projects.

German Contributor

Jet Airways / EveryMundo, Mumbai

Jan 2016 - Mar 2016

Responsible for adding to and editing German descriptions of Indian travel destinations offered by India's major airline, Jet Airways.

German Translator

Education First. London

Dec 2014 - Current

Professionally involved in translating e-books, blogs, online articles, and social media content from English into German for language learning programs at Education First, Englishtown, and English Live.

EDUCATION

English and American Studies

Chemnitz University of Technology, Chemnitz, Germany

2010 - 2013

Bachelor of Arts in English and American Studies

International Relations

Instituto Tecnológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey, Puebla, Mexico

2013 - 2013

Semester Abroad

LANGUAGES

German: Native Spanish: Fluent English: Native-like French: Basic